export const QuestionsArray = [
    { 

    },
    {
        id: "1",
        question: "what is a noun?",
        options: [
            "a noun is a name of a person, animal, place or thing","place","things"
        ],
        answer: "a noun is a name of a person, animal, place or thing"
    },
    {
        id: "2",
        question: "what is a pronoun?",
        options: [
            "pro animal","a pronoun is a word used in place of a noun","things"
        ],
        answer: "a pronoun is a word used in place of a noun"
    },
    {
        id: "3",
        question: "what is a adverb?",
        options: [
            "adverb are words used in place of a noun","adverb are words used in place of a verb","things"
        ],
        answer: "adverb are words used in place of a verb"
    },
    {
        id: "4",
        question: "what is a verb?",
        options: [
            "adverb animal","a verb is an anyhow word","a verb is an action word"
        ],
        answer: "a verb is an action word"
    },
    {
        id: "5",
        question: "what is a adjective?",
        options: [
            "adjective animal","adjectives are words used to describe a noun","adjectives are words used to describe a verb"
        ],
        answer: "adjectives are words used to describe a noun"
    },
    {
        id: "6",
        question: "what is a noun?",
        options: [
            "a noun is a name of a person, animal, place or thing","place","things"
        ],
        answer: "a noun is a name of a person, animal, place or thing"
    },
    {
        id: "7",
        question: "what is a pronoun?",
        options: [
            "pro animal","a pronoun is a word used in place of a noun","things"
        ],
        answer: "a pronoun is a word used in place of a noun"
    },
    {
        id: "8",
        question: "what is a adverb?",
        options: [
            "adverb are words used in place of a noun","adverb are words used in place of a verb","things"
        ],
        answer: "adverb are words used in place of a verb"
    },
    {
        id: "9",
        question: "what is a verb?",
        options: [
            "adverb animal","a verb is an anyhow word","a verb is an action word"
        ],
        answer: "a verb is an action word"
    },
    {
        id: "10",
        question: "what is a adjective?",
        options: [
            "adjective animal","adjectives are words used to describe a noun","adjectives are words used to describe a verb"
        ],
        answer: "adjectives are words used to describe a noun"
    },
    {
        id: "11",
        question: "what is a noun?",
        options: [
            "a noun is a name of a person, animal, place or thing","place","things"
        ],
        answer: "a noun is a name of a person, animal, place or thing"
    },
    {
        id: "12",
        question: "what is a pronoun?",
        options: [
            "pro animal","a pronoun is a word used in place of a noun","things"
        ],
        answer: "a pronoun is a word used in place of a noun"
    },
    {
        id: "13",
        question: "what is a adverb?",
        options: [
            "adverb are words used in place of a noun","adverb are words used in place of a verb","things"
        ],
        answer: "adverb are words used in place of a verb"
    },
    {
        id: "14",
        question: "what is a verb?",
        options: [
            "adverb animal","a verb is an anyhow word","a verb is an action word"
        ],
        answer: "a verb is an action word"
    },
    {
        id: "15",
        question: "what is a adjective?",
        options: [
            "adjective animal","adjectives are words used to describe a noun","adjectives are words used to describe a verb"
        ],
        answer: "adjectives are words used to describe a noun"
    }
]